So friends, ICICI LBAT has disclosed its quarter 2
numbers.  So let's
see what's inside the Quarter 2 numbers.
But before that let me tell you that the company has
also announced dividend
in this quarter.  The company is going to give you dividend at the rate of ₹6.5.  The
record date for you is going to be
23rd October.  So remember,
October 23 is the record date for the company's
₹6.5 dividend.  Let's look at the company's numbers.
I'm telling you in the cross in Data Lacks.
So see,
in the last quarter the company had generated total income of ₹683 crores.
Last year it was around Rs 5850 crore,
whereas if you look at it now, you can see the total income of the company
going up to Rs 6582 crore.
So if you look at the total income of the company,
you will see it increasing year after year.
You can roughly say that you will see an increase of around 12 to 13%
in the total income of the company, whereas if we go on quarterly basis,
here also the total income of the company was
seen increasing by around 8%.
So the total income of the company is
seen increasing quarter by quarter for the last 10 years.  Let us
talk about the premium income of the company
because basically this is the most important thing
for the company.  So
in the last quarter the company had generated Rs 5136 crore.
Last year it was around Rs 525 crore,
whereas now if you look at it you will see Rs 5651 crore.
So if you look at the premium income of the company,
you will see it increasing year after year and quarter after quarter.
Let us see what the expenses are.
So look, if we
talk about the last quarter,
in the last quarter the company basically did
not know how to spend anything here.
Sorry, please forgive me.  If we look at the last quarter, the
company's expenses in the last quarter were
around Rs 5429 crore as against Rs
5186 crore last year.  Whereas if you look at it now, you can see the company's
expenses going up to Rs 5830 crore.
So if we look at the expenses, the
company's expenses are seen to be a little higher in this quarter
and it is not that
you will see more expenses of the company at one particular place, it means that it is a little
higher at every place due to which the
net expenses are seen to be a little higher every year.
Let us
see what the net profit of the company is.
So see, in the last quarter the company was
in profit of Rs 747 crore.  Last year it was
around Rs 693 crore, whereas if you look at it now,
you saw Rs 819 crore going away.  So if you
look at the profit of the company,
you will see it increasing year after year.
You can expect a growth of around 16%
in the company's profits.  If we look at the quarters, the
company's profit is seen increasing by around 10% even at the quarterly level.
So if you look at the profit of the company,
you can see a significant increase in the profit year after year and quarter after
quarter.  However, if we
look at the operational level, the
company is a loss making company.  Basically this is also
because when you subtract the company's expenses from the company's revenue, the
company was in loss of Rs 293 crore in the last quarter.
Last year it was worth Rs 160 crore, whereas now if we
look at it, it is going into a loss of Rs 178 crore.
So in such a situation, you can see that the
loss of the company at the operational level is increasing year after year.   It is
seen decreasing on a quarterly basis.
However, the company's profit
in this quarter is around ₹819 crore,
whereas the market estimate was
approximately ₹780 crore.
So you are getting to see it slightly better than the market Karwa.  Let's
talk about EPS,
see, in the last quarter the
company's EPS was ₹15.6, last year ₹14.5, if you
look at it now, you can see it going up to ₹16.49.
And basically if we talk about NPA, then the
company has not given anything here in the NPA section.
So we cannot compare this.
So if seen overall, the numbers are
not anything special.  Today, the numbers for ICICI potential
also came.  Meaning there were some numbers of this type.  There was
no rise or fall in the stock.  So that's the type of
number that will cause you to see a 2% up or a 2%
down.
I think there should be something more than that.  Let's
see how the market reacts to this.  That's all for
today.  If you like the video, please
like it.  Also,
please subscribe to the channel.  Thank you.